Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
What?! Eren Senpai's missing?
I only turned my back for one second...
It's hard to believe that easily scared
Eren Senpai would go off on her own.
Well, it makes sense if she was scared.
It's dangerous here, ya know?
Maybe she noticed the tension
in the air and ran off.
You're making sense for a change.
Not bad for a deadhead.
Don't say that!
I know that better than anyone else...
Sorry to interrupt.
Allow me to introduce
the newest member of our group.
I'm Rika Suzuki. Nice to meet y'all.
Oh!
Ay, Omi Jin, was it?
Sorry 'bout the other day.
You gave me a huge wake-up call, though.
Huh?
What you said to me that day,
towards someone who tried to kill you...
See ya! Hope you stay alive, Suzuki-san!
Thanks, Omi Jin. I owe you for making
Rika Suzuki become human again.
N-Nah. I didn't do nothin'...
Your leg...
Oh, it was in exchange for my Prime Right.
She possesses the Evasion Right,
which nullifies any kind of physical harm.
Stand next to her and you'll
also be protected by extension.
Great.
From now on, let's station Rika
and Omi in our location for the day.
We can use the Rejection Right
and Evasion Right to protect us.
Right. Now back to Eren Senpai...
You think she'll come back on her own?
Well, that was easy. No rebuttals?
Should we wait until tomorrow, then?
They trust him.
Huh?
Saneatsu Narita... Not an owner of a
Prime Right or any significant titles.
And yet, his peers all respect and trust him.
Interesting, isn't it?
Huh...
Saneatsu...
What's up, Saaya?
Prime
Right
I found this.
Prime
Right
A Prime Right envelope?!
It was in this building.
I thought about opening it,
but I couldn't stop thinking of
what I'd have to sacrifice, and...
Prime
Right
No need to apologize.
That's totally reasonable.
Prime
Right
If I just open it myself...
Saneatsu?! What are you—
I promised I'd defeat
the Emperor... that I'd fight!
W-Wait! Let's think about this.
What're you two love birds talking about?
Hey! Don't tell me that's...
Prime
Right
Is that a Prime Right?
Perfect timing! Kazuhiko,
you're on defense. Block Saaya!
M'kay!
Defense! Defense! Defense!
Umm...
Saaya, don't worry. This is what I want.
I'm such a fool.
How could I forget why I became
a teacher in the first place?
I won't lose my way again!
This must be it.
Huh?! What's this note?
Here goes nothing...
What? Even if that's true, how could...
I have to tell him before it's too late!
Prime Right Access Denied
You are not permitted to
acquire a Prime Right.
Huh?
Prime Right Access Denied
I can't acquire a Prime Right?
I have to hurry and tell Narita!
An error when acquiring Prime Rights?
Do you have any idea what might cause it?
Hmm... Beats me.
Maybe only if you already
have a Prime Right...
or you happen to fall into another
special rule that blocks you.
Those are the only
possibilities I can think of.
Omi-kun, if you don't mind,
could you tell us everything you know
about the Camp and Prime Rights?
Of course.
The Camp is at the border
between Tokyo and Chiba.
It's a giant facility built
100 meters underground.
100 meters?!
A giant facility hidden
beneath the metro area...
The facility was designed so that no one
would find it. There were ten areas.
I was at Area A.
I never saw Sensei and that macho guy,
so they must be from another area.
Why were you there in the first place?
I'm originally from the Tohoku Region...
a small town in Aomori.
Five years ago, some men
came to visit our home.
Apparently, they'd been
introduced to my dad's company.
They were there to recruit my dad.
He gladly agreed and we all left together
as a family, in hopes of a better future.
My memory gets fuzzy after that,
and before I knew it...
Wha—
Dad? Mom? Where are ya?!
Shut up!
The Camp targeted isolated households
in rural areas with little to no relatives
so it would be harder to track,
and used them in their experiments.
They tricked my entire family.
I was forced into the lab every month
without ever seeing them.
They threatened to kill
my family if I didn't listen.
And that lasted three years...
Let's see... What if we sacrificed...
Your right eye, perhaps?
If you resist, I'll just
make it more "efficient".
Damn it, I missed.
Aww, that's too bad.
The stab went so deep that
I lost hearing in my right ear.
You mean that band aid is...
It's how I hide the scar.
After that, I was so desperate
to relieve the pain and fear
that I accessed my Prime Right.
They only experimented on the most tractable member of the family.
To prevent the rest from conspiring...
they were killed.
Because of me, both of my parents died...
Omi...
That's bullshit!
No way it's your fault!
None of it would've happened
if it wasn't for them!
Screw those fat, flaming,
stinking pieces of garbage!
And... and... Argh!
This really pisses me off!
Hey, pea size!
Don't waste time crying! Get pissed!
We'll make sure to kick their ass together!
Dammit, I'm still so pissed off!
Let's get you cooled down, okay?
Can you believe those guys?!
Now, now. Here, vent to me.
I get how you feel, though.
Hey... come on! Let go!
You take it from here!
I'm still pissed, you know!
Omi, is there anything else
you can tell us about the Camp?
It used to have branches
overseas, too, but now...
There was a huge breach
at the facility two years ago.
That was when we all escaped.
But most of us were captured.
I reported the facility wherever
I could, but no one believed me.
I see...
Here's my theory.
The Camp's objective was
to find certain Prime Rights,
and they forced prisoners
to acquire powers in search of it.
The Emperor must be the success.
What do you mean?
Aren't there only 65 Prime Rights?
I've seen the Storage Room before.
These weren't just a couple hundred
envelopes... there were way more.
Jeez. Can you imagine if you had all of them?
"All of them"? Hang on...
Omi, how many prisoners would
you say there were? A bunch?
Huh? Well, ya...
What do you think happened
to the ones who were captured?
Well, I'd assume they were all killed...
And what happens to a
Prime Right if the owner dies?
Omi, would there be any other way
to acquire Prime Rights?
Opening the envelope is the only way.
Oh, but I guess you could
be threatened to open it.
Or someone else could
make you open one by force,
if the body part in exchange is visible.
But you can only own one
Prime Right per person.
Don't you see?
The point is to have the general
public open the envelopes,
then kill them to recover
the abandoned Prime Rights.
Of course, I get it now!
The Emperor already has a Prime Right,
meaning they can't open other envelopes!
So they scattered the remaining envelopes
for other people to open!
Exactly. The Emperor's Prime Right
is likely the Recovery Right.
And their goal is to recover
other Prime Rights.
Recovery Right?
Prime Rights are limited to one per person,
Prime       Right
Recovery      Right
but as long as the Emperor
is set as the recovery destination,
they can collect as many
Prime Rights as they want.
Prime
Tasuketsu was likely made possible
due to the collected powers
of those numerous Prime Rights!
Prime
But this is all just a theory
based on the assumption
that people lose ownership
of Prime Rights when they die.
Then we'll have to prove that's the case.
Which is why we'll have to
see him again to be sure...
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Ren Iruga.
Maybe I made a mistake,
but there's no way we can find
one laptop in the whole of Kita Ward.
Hey, look. A girl!
What are you thinking?
I guess we can have some fun
before killing her.
I'll go ahead, then...
You two, crash into that convenience store!
As you wish!
Hey!
It only worked on one?!
You bitch!
You there, are you hurt?
There, there. Good job.
Isn't this the guy with
the Materialization Right?
It's safe here. No need to be afraid.
I don't plan to hurt any normal people.
Wait, he doesn't recognize me?
Oh, I'm sorry. Thank you for helping me.
You swooped in out of nowhere
like a hero. I'm still in shock.
Hero, huh...
What's the matter?
What would you do if...
if someone you considered
a hero sold his soul?
Are you talking about a manga or something?
'Course not. It's about
a man who saved my life.
I'll never forget that day, ten years ago...
I accidentally caused a fire at my house.
H-Help... me...
Anyone here?!
Hey! You okay?!
Are you all right?
Does it hurt anywhere?!
I was... cooking and...
It was my fault. I'm sorry!
You're safe. That's all that matters!
Forget about anything else!
I liked to cook, but I'm gonna quit.
This all happened cause
I wanted to make family happy...
Don't say that!
Huh?
Look...
Wanting to do something
for others is a good thing.
I feel like you'd be a good teacher.
Huh?
You'd be one of those teachers that
protects every student, like a hero!
You think so?
Yeah!
He left without even telling me his name.
A few years later, we met again
at the Ca—I mean, at a facility.
Fate had changed him by then.
He may be a hero in my eyes,
but he's still human.
I couldn't blame him for wanting to survive.
Whether it was murder or destruction,
I told myself it was to repay him
for saving my life. But...
I wonder if this is really...
Who knew Shinozaki Sensei had
such a passionate side to him?
Wha—When did you figure that out?
From the beginning, of course!
It was obvious you were just pretending to
run into me to gauge if Sensei was with me.
Why you—
You should give him
a good smack on the face.
What?
If he goes back to the hero you loved, great.
If not, do as you please.
Cook him for all I care.
Cook? Man, you sure are a weird one.
Weird and complex, just how humans
should be. You should remember that!
Do me a favor.
Can you take me to your group?
Huh?
Shinozaki-san will likely use
his Prime Right to come find me.
I want to settle things in front of you guys.
Just one condition. Tell me
about your Materialization Right.
Sure, no problem.
Oh, well that was easy.
My Materialization Right is a Prime Right
that brings drawings
and pictures to real life.
Creatures are under my full command,
which is why I carry card games
on me as my primary weapon.
But it's exhausting, since
it's under the Protection Attribute.
Not to mention, I've sacrificed my right lung.
So I can only use my powers
three or four times a day.
He sure talks a lot...
You know, I can tell that you're pretty dumb.
You could tell?! Just how much
do you already know?!
Yikes...
Oh, well. I have something
to show you guys anyways.
Better hurry and find them.
But isn't it dangerous?
Don't worry, you'll be with me.
You're Shinozaki-san's precious student.
I won't let anything happen to you.
You really believe you'll meet
your hero again, don't you?
You're that guy from—
You must be Saneatsu Narita!
I'm Hayato Souma. Nice to meet you.
Eren Senpai, get away from him!
Wait, hang on!
Simmer down. I just wanna talk.
A red laptop?! Fine...
Well, if there's no way you'll trust me,
I can just hand over this—
Stop!
Don't do anything else!
There's a possibility that a man
named Mido will steal your laptop
the moment you abandon ownership of it.
We sure don't want that.
Regardless, coming into possession
of a laptop is the hardest part.
Lucky for us, you've found one already.
Here, take the adapter.
There's no remaining battery, so
there's no using the laptop without this.
You can be sure it's safe.
I've entered the password so we're fine
until the end of the day tomorrow.
Haven't submitted any questions, either.
That should make it safe.
With Souma as the current owner,
we have no choice
but to stick with him
to protect the laptop—
What is it?
Shinozaki-san...
Souma... Why are you with Narita?
No! It's not what you think!
Shinozaki-san!
I've decided to work with them
to defeat the Emperor.
What about you?
Souma...
Let's settle this,
in front of the students you betrayed.
I'm sorry!
I won't ask for forgiveness.
I don't expect you to forgive me.
It was all entirely my wrongdoing.
Shinozaki-san...
We can't accept that after all you've—
Of course not! But please,
believe what I'm about to tell you!
Sudo is dead!
Sudo Senpai?!
That can't be...
Do you have any proof?
Any messages or belongings he left you?
I have documents and notes he
entrusted me with. Other than that...
I remember him using
a special type of fire powder.
Something about magicians
and his friend lending it to him...
That's more than enough.
I believe Sensei is telling the truth.
President?!
The rest of you don't need to believe him.
But trust me when I say he's being truthful.
I trust him, too.
All right. So?
According to Sudo's notes, the Emperor's
Prime Right is the Recovery Right,
and their objective is
to recover other Prime Rights.
Senpai had the same theory...
So why did Tasuketsu begin
in Suginami of all places?
That's because "Saneatsu Narita
was in Suginami".
Huh?
What?
What does that mean?
Sudo went on to say this:
Saneatsu Narita should already
possess some kind of Prime Right.
That thought crossed my mind, too!
That would explain why
I couldn't open the envelope...
It all began with this.
A newspaper clipping?
An article about my accident
from when I was four...
What?!
"...caused by the father's friend"
It was caused by my dad's friend?
You never knew?
Sudo's theory was this:
Narita's father hired his friend
to cause the accident and harm you.
But why would my dad do that?
These are your medical records
from the accident.
Saneatsu Narita's Medical Records
It says right here...
"Saneatsu Narita: Loss of one kidney due to
injuries sustained in the accident."
Loss of one kidney due to injuries sustained in the accident
"Loss"? You mean...
Most likely, he used your surgery as
a means to forcefully sacrifice your kidney
in return for a Prime Right!
How could that be possible?!
I never even told Sudo Senpai
about my accident!
Sudo first took notice of Jin and myself.
Oh, is that cuz I already had a Prime Right?
Yes.
Prime Right
Prime Rights directly relate to Tasuketsu,
and Tasuketsu directly relates to the Emperor.
Tasuketsu
Emperor
Assuming the Emperor intentionally
began Tasuketsu in Suginami...
Suginami Ward
...led Sudo to this.
Gunjosora Orphanage
Children's Home
Gunjosora Orphanage!
Wait, pea size. You know this place?
After I escaped the Camp,
they took care of me.
For real?! They took me in, too!
Me, as well.
The Director is named Yugo Shimahara.
Suspect Yugo Shimahara
He's the man who hit Narita.
A friend of Dad's... An orphanage...
A kidney in return for a Prime Right...
Is your dad still living overseas?
It used to have branches overseas, too...
Prime Right Access Denied
I can't acquire a Prime Right?
The more I think about it,
the more it makes sense...
Saneatsu...
And the note also states this:
Narita Saneatsu
is the key
The Prime Right entrusted to Narita
should be the key to defeating the Emperor.
So Narita-kun's father was taking up
arms against the organization
while being a member himself.
Precisely.
He knew that the birth of a
successful subject was imminent,
so he passed down the only
hope he had to his own son.
But I thought you couldn't
know what Prime Rights are
in each envelope for real until you open it.
How did he choose Saneatsu's Prime Right?
Sudo suspected there was another collaborator
with a Prime Right that made it possible.
Perhaps a researcher who
provided help in a limited scope
under certain conditions and circumstances.
That's a crazy-detailed theory, for real...
That's the overall picture.
The details are still unclear. There's just
too many elements intertwined in the story.
Either way, we have our hope right here!
Saneatsu Narita is the key to everything!
Engage Transillumination Right.
Right
Portrait
Aww, man. Another fail.
Assemble
Too bad.